7:30 through the ticket gate
改札抜けた朝の光
Voices bleeding through my earphones
眠気と戦いながら
Convenience store lights pull me in
Like a moth to artificial flame
ツナマヨおにぎり minus 128円
BOSS缶コーヒー minus 110円
That's my breakfast
That's my choice
誰も知らない僕の選択
Nobody knows the weight I carry
西荻窪から東京
minus 380円
東京から西荻窪
Every transaction tells a story
感情よりも正確な数字で
日々がレシートに並んでく
These numbers don't lie but they can't cry
LINE notification cuts the silence
鳥貴族 予約なしじゃ入れないらしい
だけど今夜も無言のまま
My bed and fridge, my only friends
In this city of eight million souls
I'm still learning how to be alone
セブン弁当 のり弁当
minus 498円
ファミマ チュール、おにぎり minus
120円
ドトール ブレンドコーヒーS minus
224円
スタバ ドリップコーヒートール
minus 350円
But then, but then
お母さん 振込 5000円
お母さん 振込 3000円
That's the only warmth I know
ahamoから通知
残り2ギガバイト
Communication limits can't contain
What I can't say anyway
明治おいしい牛乳1L minus
228円
卵Mサイズ10個
minus 298円
超熟食パン6枚切り
minus 170円
At least that part is real
Weekend delivery
佐川急便
佐川の荷物。温かくしてねって
Hand cream from mama's hands
値段じゃないよって
でも送料込み
2180円が
ちょっとだけ泣けた
Made me remember
I'm still somebody's child
西荻窪から東京
minus 380円
東京から西荻窪
ローソン カフェラテS minus
150円
東京ばな奈 8個入り minus
1029円
Tokyo souvenirs for no one
誰も見てない履歴の中
ちゃんと僕は今日を生きてる
セブンイレブン 天然水
500ml
minus 108円
花キューピット ガーベラ3本
minus 880円
Small acts of hope
お母さん
振込 4000円
振込 6000円
愛されてたことに
I'm learning what love looks like
In bank transfer
notifications
いま気づく
Receipt paper fading
But the feeling remains
These numbers, these days
They're proof I was here